const myCardsTitle = [
  {
    levelNumber: "1.10",
    title: "Cardinal Numbers",
  },
];

const myCards = [
  {
    front: "jeden 1",
    back: "one 1",
  },

  {
    front: "dwa 2",
    back: "two 2",
  },

  {
    front: "trzy 3",
    back: "three 3",
  },

  {
    front: "cztery 4",
    back: "four 4",
  },

  {
    front: "pięć 5",
    back: "five 5",
  },

  {
    front: "sześć 6",
    back: "six 6",
  },

  {
    front: "siedem 7",
    back: "seven 7",
  },

  {
    front: "osiem 8",
    back: "eight 8",
  },

  {
    front: "dziewięć 9",
    back: "nine 9",
  },

  {
    front: "dziesięć 10",
    back: "ten 10",
  },

  {
    front: "jedenaście 11",
    back: "eleven 11",
  },

  {
    front: "dwanaście 12",
    back: "twelve 12",
  },

  {
    front: "trzynaście 13",
    back: "thirteen 13",
  },

  {
    front: "czternaście 14",
    back: "fourteen 14",
  },

  {
    front: "piętnaście 15",
    back: "fifteen 15",
  },

  {
    front: "szesnaście 16",
    back: "sixteen 16",
  },

  {
    front: "siedemnaście 17",
    back: "seventeen 17",
  },

  {
    front: "osiemnaście 18",
    back: "eighteen 18",
  },

  {
    front: "dziewiętnaście 19",
    back: "nineteen 19",
  },

  {
    front: "dwadzieścia 20",
    back: "twenty 20",
  },

  {
    front: "dwadzieścia jeden 21",
    back: "twenty-one 21",
  },

  {
    front: "trzydzieści 30",
    back: "thirty 30",
  },

  {
    front: "czterdzieści 40",
    back: "forty 40",
  },

  {
    front: "pięćdziesiąt 50",
    back: "fifty 50",
  },

  {
    front: "pięćdziesiąt pięć 55",
    back: "fifty-five 55",
  },

  {
    front: "sześćdziesiąt 60",
    back: "sixty 60",
  },

  {
    front: "siedemdziesiąt 70",
    back: "seventy 70",
  },

  {
    front: "osiemdziesiąt 80",
    back: "eighty 80",
  },

  {
    front: "dziewięćdziesiąt 90",
    back: "ninety 90",
  },

  {
    front: "sto 100",
    back: "a hundred 100",
  },
];

export { myCardsTitle, myCards };
